

Uğur Dindar Software Engineer

101/23/2001

Turkey and Bulgaria Citizen

• Eskişehir, Turkey

wugurdindar.com

in linkedin.com/in/ugurdindar/

github.com/Tzesh

■ mail@ugurdindar.com

₽ Profile

I am a goal-oriented, self-disciplined, hard-working person who has developed a mature and responsible approach to any task that I undertake, or situation that I am presented with. A team member who can establish and maintain good teamwork by working as a part of the team. Skilled at quickly solving problems, pursuing and uncovering new solutions to old or/and tough problems, and effectively communicating. A software developer who is capable of designing, and developing complex systems with ease. Strong background in project management and customer relations. Especially qualified, experienced and proven himself in programming knowledge, back-end and front-end technologies. Well-versed in multiple programming languages. Always a student who has a curiosity and open to learn new things.

Professional Experience

Software Developer, *Garanti BBVA Technology*

06/2023 – present | İstanbul, Turkey

I'm currently working as a Software Developer in Garanti BBVA Technology. I'm in a team that is responsible for developing and maintaining ACS (3D Secure) operations of Garanti BBVA also VPOS (Virtual POS) systems.

Software Developer, *Ford Otosan* □

10/2021 – 06/2023 | Eskişehir, Turkey

I have been working as Software Developer in other words Full Stack Developer in Ford Otosan since October 2021. I have participated in the development of several projects in which their backend technologies are based on .NET MVC, .NET Web Forms, and .NET Core. On the other hand, I have developed the front-end of the projects with HTML, CSS, and JS. I am experienced in PL/SQL, Oracle Toad, and Azure DevOps.

Software Engineering Intern, *Baykar Technology* □

08/2021 – 09/2021 | İstanbul, Turkey

I have worked as a Software Engineering Intern in 'Baykar Technology' which is one of the lead defense industry companies in Turkey. I had developed several projects using C# and .NET technologies. I cannot tell any furthermore information about the projects that I have built but the one that I have spent much more time on than others is generally automation of some kind of OS/Software adjustments.

Canguages **English Turkish** Bilingual proficiency Native proficiency German Elementary proficiency

Education

Bachelor's Degree, Eskişehir Technical University 09/2019 – 06/2023 | Eskişehir, Turkey Computer Engineering, GPA: 3.70 - Graduated as 1st in the Computer Engineering Department

Skills

Front-end

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, React, Bootstrap, JQuery, Next

Tools

Git, Azure DevOps, Toad

Other

Competitive Programming

Certificates

Scrum Team Member □

Awards

OBSS Code Master 2021 2nd all across Eskişehir Technical University, OBSS

Projects

Virtual Patient,

Virtual patient app that allows nurses to get experience in practical applications of patient care □

Quality Pool, *Graduation project (Tübitak 2209-B)*

Management, classification and solution suggestion platform for warranty and quality processes in the automotive industry which will be used in Ford Otosan

Denpointment, A fully-working dentist appointment system which is written in Python using Flask web development, powered by Bootstrap, using MySQL to manipulate data. ♂

The rest of the projects that I have developed listed on my GitHub profile. □

Back-end

.NET Framework, .NET Core, Flask, Express, Spring, Spring Boot, PL/SQL, MySQL, MongoDB

Interpersonal

Communication, Teamwork, Organization, Critical Thinking, Always Punctual, Problem Solving